Inventory of the Sheila Tobias Women's Studies Collection, 1937 - 1977; bulk 1970-1975
Sheila Tobias Women's Studies Collection1937 - 1977; bulk 1970-1975
- Series 1: Authors Files
  - Money, John and Zubin, Joseph, Contemporary Sexual Behavior: Critical Issues in the 1970s, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Money, John, Determinants of Human Sexual Identity and Behavior, 1972 (Box 19)
  - , Nativism versus Culturalism in Gender-identity Differentiation, 1972 (Box 19)
  - , Clinical Aspects of Prenatal Steroidal Action on Sexually Dimorphic Behavior, 1972 (Box 19)
  - , Differentiation of Gender Identity and Gender Role, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Montgomery, Judith, The American Galatea, undated (Box 19)
  - Moran, Robert D., Women at Work Reducing Discrimination: role of the Equal Pay Act, undated (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Elaine, The Descent of Woman, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Morrison, Toni, "What the Black Woman Thinks About Women's Lib" New York Times, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Moseley, Eva, "Women in Archives: Documenting the History of Women in America" American Archivist, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Moskoff, William, An Estimate of the Soviet Male-Female Income Gap, undated (Box 19)
  - , Proposal for Women Studies Committee, undated (Box 19)
  - Moursund, David, "Calculators in the Elementary School" Math Learning Center Report, 1977 (Box 19)
  - , Moving Out: Feminist Literary and Art Journal, 1974 (Box 19)
  - MSS Women's Guide to Books, The Women's Guide to Books, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Mulligan, Joan, Three Federal Interventions on Behalf of Childbearing Women: The Sheppard-Towner Act, Emergency Maternal and Infant Care, and the Maternal and Child Health and Mental Retardation Planning Amendments of 1963, undated (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Mary, "Superstar Women and their Marriages" New York Magazine, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Pauli, Economic and Educational Inequality Based on Sex: An Overview, undated (Box 19)
  - National Coalition for Research on Women's Education and Developtment, Description of the National Coalition for Research on Women's Education and Development, undated (Box 19)
  - , Comment on Changing Patriarchy, 1974 (Box 19)
  - , Conference Program, 1972 (Box 19)
  - The Need for a New Organization, Proposal, undated (Box 20)
  - Newell, Barbara W., Social Pressures on Management: Equal Opportunity for Employment, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Newman, Lucille, Unwanted Pregnancy: Some Cultural Considerations, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Newsweek Special Report, "Gloria Steinem: A Liberated Woman Despite Beauty, Chic, and Success" Newsweek Special Report, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich, Woman De-Feminized, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Nissen, Iingjald, The Role of the Sexual Constellation, undated (Box 20)
  - Nochlin, Linda, "Why are there no great women artists?" Woman at Work, undated (Box 20)
  - , Why have there been no great women artists?, undated (Box 20)
  - , Women Artists of the Nineteenth Century, undated (Box 20)
  - No More Fun and Games: A Journal of Female Liberation, "The Dialectics of Sexism", 1969 (Box 20)
  - Noordhoek, Johannes and Smith, Yrsa, Family and Work, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Novick, Lee, A Political History of the Equal Rights Amendment, undated (Box 20)
  - Oates, Carol Joyce, Book Reviews of Towards a Recognition of Androgyny and Virginia Woolf and the Androgynous Vision, undated (Box 20)
  - O'Connor, J.J., Woman's Place, undated (Box 20)
  - , Occupations of the Employed Female Populations (datatables), undated (Box 20)
  - Oelsner, Lesley, Court Rules Social Security Aid Need Not Go to Divorced Mothers, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Olesen, Virginia and Davis, Fred, Initiation into a Women's Profession: Identity Problems in the Status Transition of Coed to Student Nurse, 1963 (Box 20)
  - , The Career Outlook of Professionally Educated Women: The Case of Collegiate Student Nurses, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Olesen, Virginia and Whittaker, Elvi, The Faces of Florence Nightingale: functions of the Heroine Legend in an Occupational Sub-Culture, 1964 (Box 20)
  - , Instant Life: Women Report on Immersion in the Adult World, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Olesen, Virginia, Militance in a Women's Profession: Psychological Characteristics of Partisans and Critics of Nurses' Strike, undated (Box 20)
  - Ohmann,, Emily Bronte in the Hands of Male Critics, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Ola D'Aulair, Emily and Per, Equal Rights Amendment: What's it All About?, undated (Box 20)
  - Olson, Iddy, Freud's Contribution to Female Oppression, undated (Box 20)
  - O'Neill, Wm., Women at Work, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Oppenheimer, V., The Sex-Labeling of Jobs, undated (Box 20)
  - Osherow, Neal, Lecture on Freud - Am. Studies 210, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Osofsky, Joy, The Shaping of Mothers' Behavior by Children, 1969 (Box 20)
  - , The Socialization and Education of American Females, 1970 (Box 20)
  - , Socialization and Sex Role Development, undated (Box 20)
  - , Psychological Reactions of Patients to Legalized Abortions, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Palme, Olaf, The Emancipation of Man, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Palmegiano, E. M., Women's Education: Subject and Object of the Mid-Victorial Press, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Pappas, Dee Ann, On being Natural, undated (Box 21)
  - Parish, W. L. Jr., Comment: The Present and Future of Women in Communist China, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Park, Clara, As We Like It: How a Girl Can Be Smart and Still Popular, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Parsons, M., Review: Astronauts and Admen: The Feminized Male, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Pelz, Edith, Her-self, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Pescatello, Ann, "The Female in Ibero-America: An Essay on Research Bibliography and Research Directions" Latin American Research Review, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Petschauer, Peter, Types of Education for Eighteenth Century Women in Southwest Germany, undated (Box 21)
  - Pettus, Isabella Mary, "The Legal Education of Women" Albany Law Journal, undated (Box 21)
  - Philipps, Betty, Women's Resource Center, New Haven - Abstract, undated (Box 21)
  - Pifer, Alan, Women in Higher Education, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Pietrofesa, John and Schlossberg, Nancy, Counselor Bias and the Female Occupational Role, undated (Box 21)
  - Piore, M., Fragments of a "Sociological" Theory of Wages, undated (Box 21)
  - Pleck, Joseph, New Concepts of Sex Role Identity, 1973 (Box 21)
  - , Berkeley Men's Center Manifesto, undated (Box 21)
  - , Male Sex Role and Personality - Historical Materials, 1973 (Box 21)
  - , On the Politics of Male Liberation, 1971 (Box 21)
  - , Psychological Frontiers for Men, 1973 (Box 21)
  - , Psychosocial Change in Men, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Plotkin, Sarah, De Beauvoir's The Second Sex: Her Existentialist Approach, 1977 (Box 21)
  - , Political Economy of Women, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Poloma, Margaret and Garland, Neal, "The Married Professional Woman: A Study in the Tolerance of Domestication" Journal of Marriage and Family, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Potter, David M., American Women and the American Character, undated (Box 21)
  - Rasmuson, Marianne, "Men, the Weaker Sex?" Impact of Science on Society, undated (Box 21)
  - Rawalt, Marguerite, Support of the "Equal Rights Amendment" to the Constitution, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Rheinstein, Max, Marriage Stability, Divorce, and the Law, undated (Box 21)
  - Reed, Evelyn, The Myth of Women's Inferiority, undated (Box 21)
  - Reed, Kit, "…with his lovely wife", undated (Box 21)
  - Rich, Adrienne, Toward a Women-centered University, undated (Box 21)
  - Richardson, Stephen, "Age and Sex Differences in Values Toward Physical Handicaps" Journal of Health and Social Behavior, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Roache, Joel, "Confessions of a househusband" Ms, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Roberts, Henry L., Four Queens and Several Knaves, undated (Box 21)
  - Robinson, Lillian, The Sexual Order, 1970 (Box 22)
  - Roby, Pamela, Structural and Internalized Barriers to Women in Higher Education, undated (Box 22)
  - , The Revision, Enforcement, and Judicial Administration of New York State Penal Laws on Prostitution, 1971 (Box 22)
  - , Women and Higher Education: Historical Perspectives, undated (Box 22)
  - , Women and American Higher Education, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Roby, Pamela and Kerr, Virginia, The Politics of Prostitution, undated (Box 22)
  - Roiphe, Anne, "What Women Psychoanalysts Say About Women's Liberation" New York Times Magazine, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Rollin, Betty, Backlash against Women's Lib! "They're a Bunch of Frustrated Hags", undated (Box 22)
  - , Motherhood: Who Needs It?, 1970 (Box 22)
  - , Motherhood: Who Needs It? (Another Copy), 1970 (Box 22)
  - , So I know from Pastrami, 1973 (Box 22)
  - , "First You Cry", undated (Box 22)
  - , Cancer Misc., undated (Box 22)
  - Rose, Phyllis, Mrs. Ramsey and Mrs. Woolf, undated (Box 22)
  - Rosen, Benson and Jendee, Thomas H, Influence of Sex Role Stereotypes on Personal Decisions, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, B. G., Sex, Sex Role, and Sex Role Identity: The Built-in Paradoxes, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, Barbara, Women's Subordination in Marriage: The View from the Courts, 1970 (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, Carol, The Female Animal: A Medical and Biological View of Women and Women's Role in 19th Century America, undated (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, Caroll Smith and Rosenberg Charles E., The Female Animal: A Medical and Biological View of Women and Women's Role in 19th Century America, undated (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, Caroll Smith, Violation, Aggression and Conflict: Some Reflections on Hysteria and Women in 19th Century America, undated (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, Caroll Smith, Beauty, the Beast and the Militant Woman: A Case Study in Sex Roles and Social Stress in Jacksonian America, undated (Box 22)
  - Rosenberg, Charles E., Sexuality, Class and Role in 19th Century America, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Rosenkrantz, Paul and Vogel, Susan and Bee, Helen and Broverman, Inge, Sex-Role Stereotypes and Self-Concept in College Students, undated (Box 22)
  - , Family Size and Sex-Role Stereotypes, undated (Box 22)
  - , Sex Role Stereotypes and Clinical Judgements of Mental Health, undated (Box 22)
  - Rosenthal, Neil and Johnson, Allan, The Legal Images of Women, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Rossi, Alice, Presentations, 1969 (Box 23)
  - , The Mystique of Parenthood, 1968 (Box 23)
  - , Women Scientists: Prospects and Problems, 1966 (Box 23)
  - , Women in Science: Why so Few?, undated (Box 23)
  - , Changing Sex Roles and Family Development, 1971 (Box 23)
  - , Job Discrimination and What Women Can Do About It, 1970 (Box 23)
  - , Women in the Seventies: Problems and Possibilities, 1970 (Box 23)
  - , Sentiment and Intellect: The Story of John Stuart Mill and Harriet Taylor Mill, 1970 (Box 23)
  - , Discrimination and Demography restrict Opportunities for Academic Women, 1971 (Box 23)
  - , Equality between the Sexes: An Immodest Proposal, 1967 (Box 23)
  - , Misc., undated (Box 23)
  - , Status of Women in Graduate Departments of Sociology, 1968-1969, 1970 (Box 23)
  - , Chapter 21, Summary and Prospects, Academic Women on the Move, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Rossiter, Margaret, Women in the French Resistance 1940-1945, undated (Box 23)
  - Roth, Susan, Cases and Materials on Title VII of the 1964 Civil Rights Act for the Arms Panel on Labor Law, undated (Box 23)
  - Rothschild, Constantina, The Options of Greek Men and Women, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Rowe, Mary, Prospects and Patters for Men and Women at Work: To Be Able Both to Love and Work, 1973 (Box 23)
  - , The Saturn's Ring Phenomenon: Micro-inequities and Unequal Opportunity for Women in the American Economy, 1975 (Box 23)
  - , The Progress of Women in Educational Institutions: The Saturn's Rings Phenomenon, undated (Box 23)
  - Rudy, Arthur J. and Peller, Robert, Men's Liberation, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Rudy, Michelle, Women, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Rupp, Leila, A Repraisal of American Women in a Men's War: 1941-1945, undated (Box 23)
  - Russ, Joanna, The Image of Women in Science Fiction, undated (Box 23)
  - Russell, Michael, Rapunzel, Let Down Your Hair: An Open Letter to Women in the Academy, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Ruth, Sheila, Motherhood, Mysogyny, and Bad Faith: Sexism in the Philosophic Establishment, undated (Box 24)
  - Rynda, Eleana, Physiological Aspects of Competion for Women, undated (Box 24)
  - Sachs, J. and Lieberman, P. and Erickson, D., Anatomical and Cultural Determinants of Male and Female Speech, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Sacks, Karen, Engels Revisited: Women, the Organization of Production, and Private Property, 1974 (Box 24)
  - , Class Roots of Feminism, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Samuels, Catherine, The Forgotten Five Million: Women in Public Employment, undated (Box 24)
  - , A Guide to Eliminating Sex Discrimination, undated (Box 24)
  - Samuels, Victoria and Selfee, Nancy, Nowhere to Be Found: A Literature Review and Annotated Bibliography on White Working Class Women, 1975 (Box 24)
  - , Ephemera from the conference: "The Challenge of the Women's Movement: American Diversity, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Sandeen, Ernest R., "John Humphrey Noyes as the New Adam" Church History, undated (Box 24)
  - Sandler, Bernice, The Equal Rights Amendment and the Women's Equality Act, 1971 (Box 24)
  - , Research and Support Strategies for Women's Higher Education, 1971 (Box 24)
  - Sandler, Georgette B. and Mintz, Ellen, Consultants to the Cops: Two Feminists' Experience with "New York's Finest", 1973 (Box 24)
  - Sassower, Doris L., Women in the Law: The Second Hundred Years, 1971 (Box 24)
  - , Marital Bliss: Till Divorce Do Us Part, 1973 (Box 24)
  - , The Married Woman as Legal Victim, 1973 (Box 24)
  - , No-Fault Divorce and Women's Property Rights, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Sawyer, Jack, On Male Liberation, undated (Box 24)
  - Scarf, Maggie, He and She: The Sex Hormones and Behavior, undated (Box 24)
  - , Normality is a Square Circle or a Four-Sided Triangle, undated (Box 24)
  - Scarr-Salapatek, Sandra, Race, Social Class, and IQ, 1971 (Box 24)
  - Scher, Maryonda, Women Psychiatrists in the US, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Schlossberg, N. K., Rumblings of a Mad Feminist, 1974 (Box 24)
  - , The Right to be Wrong is Gone: Women in Academe, 1974 (Box 24)
  - , Imperative for Change: Counselor Use of the Strong Vocational Interest Blanks, undated (Box 24)
  - Schmertz, Ida F.S., Women State Legislators: Impression from a Conference, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Schmidt, Margaret, Sex Roles and Survival, undated (Box 24)
  - Schmidt, Earl Robert and Schmidt, Dolores, The Invisible Women: The Historian as Professional Magician, undated (Box 24)
  - Schmidt, Dolores Barracano, The Great American Bitch, undated (Box 24)
  - Schlotz-Klink, Gertrud, The Place of Women in the New Germany, undated (Box 24)
  - School of Education, Indiana State University, Contemporary Education: Women in Education, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Scholtz, T. Paul, Longterm Change in Personal Income Distribution: Theoretical Approaches, Evidence and Explanations, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Schulder, Diane, Women and the Law, undated (Box 24)
  - , Does the Law Oppress Women?, 1970 (Box 24)
  - Schwaber, Paul, Women and Freud's Imagination, 1972 (Box 24)
  - , Women and Freud's Imagination (2nd folder, multpiple copies, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Schwartz, Ellen Bay, Psychological Barriers to Increased Employment of Women, undated (Box 24)
  - Schwartz, Pepper, Female Sexuality and Monogamy, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Schwartz, Pepper and Lever, Janet, Masculin et Feminine: Dating Patterns on a College Campus, 1971 (Box 25)
  - , Women in the Male World of Higher Education, undated (Box 25)
  - Soctt, Ann, Feminism Vs. The Feds, undated (Box 25)
  - , Educating American Women for the Leisure Class, 1971 (Box 25)
  - , The Half-Eaten Apple: A Look at Sex Discrimination in the University, 1970 (Box 25)
  - , Assorted articles, letters and speeches, undated (Box 25)
  - Scotte, Anne Firor, Women's Perspective on the Patriarchy in the 1850s, undated (Box 25)
  - Scott-Heide, Wilma, Feminism for Healthy Social Work, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Scully, Diane and Bart, Pauline, A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Orifice: Women in Gynaecology Textbooks, 1973 (Box 25)
  - VAL, Secretaries to hold N.E. meeting here, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Seidenberg, Faith, The Woman Lawyer, 1969 (Box 25)
  - , Law Pertaining to Women in the United States, undated (Box 25)
  - Seidenberg, Robert, Oedipus and Male Supremacy, undated (Box 25)
  - , Drug Advertising and Perception of Mental Illness, 1971 (Box 25)
  - , The Trauma of Eventlessness, 1972 (Box 25)
  - , Dear Mr. Success: Consider Your Wife, 1972 (Box 25)
  - , Is Sex Possible Without Sexism?, 1972 (Box 25)
  - , Older Women and Younger Men, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Seifer, Nancy, The Challenge of the Women's Movement: American Diversity, 1975 (Box 25)
  - , Absent from the Majority: Working Class Women in America, 1973 (Box 25)
  - , Equal Rights and Working Class Women, undated (Box 25)
  - Sells, Lucy W., Sex Differences in Graduate School Survival, 1973 (Box 25)
  - , Doctoral Production, undated (Box 25)
  - Shaeffer, Ruth, Workshop on Women in the Professions, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Shafer, Susanne M., Socialization of Girls in The Secondary Schools of England and the Two Germanys, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Shainess, Natalie, Images of Woman: Past and Present, Overt and Obscured, 1969 (Box 25)
  - , Abortion is No Man's Business, undated (Box 25)
  - Sherfey, Mary Jane, The Evolution and Nature of Female Sexuality in Relation to Psychoanalytic Theory, undated (Box 25)
  - Sherman, Julia A., Socializing for Maximal Female Competence, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Shilling, Nancy A., Some Implications for Policy Formulation and Institutional Change of the Status of Women in the Contemporary Arab World, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Shostak, Arthur, Middle-Aged Working Class Americans at Home: Changing Expectations of Manhood, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Showalter, Elaine, Women and the Literary Curriculum, undated (Box 25)
  - Silviera, Jeanette, The Effect of Sexism on Thought, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Simchak, Morga MacLeod, Equal Pay in the United States, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Siskin, Sidney, Education for Survival: The University in a Technological Society, undated (Box 25)
  - Skerry, Peter N., A Proposal for Support to Explore the Political Implications of Abortion Reform Relative to Working and Lower-middle class Whites, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Skolnick, Rethinking the Family, undated (Box 25)
  - Smith, Hendrick, The Russians' 'Women': Liberated but Not Emancipated, undated (Box 26)
  - , "What is Happening to America's Women?" SNPA Foundation Seminar Books, undated (Box 26)
  - Sochen, Jane, Hollywood Movie Stars in the Thirties and Forties, undated (Box 26)
  - , Henrietta Rodman and the Feminist Alliance, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Somerville, Rose M., The Urban Working Class Woman in the USSR: An Historical Overview, undated (Box 25)
  - Sonenstein, Freya, Married Blue Collar Women: Their Perceived Satisfaction with their Jobs, Life Situations, and Marriages, undated (Box 26)
  - Sontag, Susan, The Double Standard of Aging, undated (Box 26)
  - Sopko, Sandra, Feminist Weighs 'Equality Impact' at Conference, 1973 (Box 26)
  - , Women's Rights and Lib Inseparable, YWCA Told, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Spanish Speaking Women's Concerns Group, Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare - Women's Action Program Recommendations for Implementation, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Spitz, Deborah, Freud and Erickson: Toward a Psychology of Women, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Staff Introduction, Issues in Industrial Society, Cornell University, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Stannard, Una, The Male Maternal Instinct, undated (Box 26)
  - , Married Women v. Husbands' Names: The Case for Wives who Keep Their Own Name, 1972 (Box 26)
  - , Why Little Girls Are Sugar and When They Grow Up They Become Cheesecake, 1971 (Box 26)
  - , Clothing and Sexuality: is the present Similarity in dress between Men and Women a Forecast of equality between the Sexes?, 1971 (Box 26)
  - State College Planning Commissions, Planning for Change: Statement of Possible Missions, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Stein, Aletha H. and Bailey, Margaret M., The Socialization of Achievement Motivation in Females, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Stein, Robert L., The Economic Status of Families Headed by Women, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Steinem, Gloria, Ms. Letter, undated (Box 26)
  - , Misc., undated (Box 26)
  - , Growing Up with Marilyn, undated (Box 26)
  - Steinem, Gloria, Women Voters can't be Trusted, undated (Box 26)
  - Steinmetz, U. G., The Male Mystique, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Stern, Milton, The Humanities and Public Policy, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Stevens, Linda, Early Sex Role Socialization of Children, undated (Box 26)
  - Stimpson, Catharine R., The New Feminism and Women's Studies, 1973 (Box 26)
  - , What Matter Mind: A Theory about the Practice of Women's Studies, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Storrs, Uconn Dismisses Female Provost, undated (Box 26)
  - Stouffer, Samuel, The American Soldier "Ground Troop Combat Motivation", 1949 (Box 26)
  - Strain, Barbara, Loners' Discuss Future of Women's Studies, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Straub, Eleanor Ferguson, The Impact of World War II on Women in the United States, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Strindberg, August, The Vampire Wife, undated (Box 26)
  - Strober, Myra H., The Earnings and Promotion of Women Faculty, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Student Papers, Women in the Youth Culture (Weitzman) VAL, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Sugg, Redding, Lillian Smith and the Condition of Women, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Sullerot, Evelyne, The Male Narcissus: A Parisian Gasp, undated (Box 26)
  - Swarthmore College Bulletin, Alumni Issue, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Swift, David E., Voices Crying in the American Wilderness: Studies in Aloneness and Radicalism, undated (Box 27)
  - Szasz, Thomas, "Theology, Witchcraft, and Hysteria" Myth and Mental Illness, undated (Box 27)
  - Tay, Alice Erh-soon, The Status of Women in the Soviet Union, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Taylor, Suzanne, Application for NEA and C.V., 1974 (Box 27)
  - , Sexual Oppression of Women in Education, undated (Box 27)
  - Tennov, Dorothy, Mode of Control and Reinforcement Density as Function of the Sex of the Behaver, undated (Box 27)
  - , Vita, undated (Box 27)
  - , Who the Hell Does She Think She Is? - Women Speaking, 1972 (Box 27)
  - , The Women's Movement: Tip of the Iceberg, 1972 (Box 27)
  - , Women and the Analysis of the Behavior Environment, 1972 (Box 27)
  - , The Relationship Between Obstetrical Procedures and Perinatal Anoxia, 1974 (Box 27)
  - , Patriarchal Control over Female Body Functions and Creation of Female Criminals, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Thompson, Clara, "Penis Envy" in Women, 1976 (Box 27)
  - T, The American Family: Future Uncertain, 1970 (Box 27)
  - Time Magazine, Special Issue: The American Woman, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Tipton, Frank B., Origins of Agrarianism: The Size and Regional Distribution of the Agricultural Labor Force in Germany 1861-1907, undated (Box 27)
  - Tishman, Artemus, "The Masculinity Myth" Syllabus, undated (Box 27)
  - Tobach, Ethel, Some Evolutionary Aspects of Human Gender, 1971 (Box 27)
  - Tobias, Sheila, Education Women for Leadership, undated (Box 27)
  - , Black and White Women in Employment - Social Roles of Women in America, undated (Box 27)
  - , Female Studies -- An Immodest Proposal, undated (Box 27)
  - , The Impact of Equality, 1973 (Box 27)
  - , Review of Arno Series for Ms. Magazine, undated (Box 27)
  - , Women in Eastern Europe: Some Impressions, 1976 (Box 27)
  - , Women at Work, 1971 (Box 27)
  - , What is Women's History, undated (Box 27)
  - , Testimony on Status of Women, 1973 (Box 27)
  - , Women's Studies Conference transcription of talks by Florence Howe and Rita Mae Brown, 1973 (Box 27)
  - , Woman as Sex Object, 1970 (Box 27)
  - , Notes (Masculinity and Violence), undated (Box 27)
  - , Quick Run-Down of Federal Legislation Re: Discrimination Against Women, undated (Box 27)
  - , The Independent Woman: An Analysis of The Group by Mary McCarthy and The Golden Notebook by Doris Lessing, undated (Box 27)
  - , Women and the Law (Research), undated (Box 27)
  - , Blue Collar Woman, undated (Box 28)
  - , Women's Liberation Phase II, 1972 (Box 28)
  - , History of Women Part I, undated (Box 28)